[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Juliet 'i melt with you' was which band's signature hit released on their 'after the snow' album in 1982",
    "Answer": "Modern english"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": "Honolulu\" means _____________",
    "Answer": "Sheltered harbor"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "How many gallons of fuel does a jumbo jet use during take off?",
    "Answer": "Four thousand"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "In the game of cricket which bird name means scoring no runs",
    "Answer": "Duck"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "With which singer did Westlife record a version of Against all Odds in 2000?",
    "Answer": "Mariah Carey"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "In 1951 Howard Hawks Produced The Thing. Who Directed The 1982 remake, Starring Kurt Russell",
    "Answer": "John Carpenter"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "The Paris stock exchange",
    "Answer": "Bourse"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "What amendment to the u.s. constitution ended prohibition",
    "Answer": "The twenty first"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What game of chance was originally called 'Beano'",
    "Answer": "Bingo"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "Where Did Napoleon Bonaparte Die In Exile?",
    "Answer": "St Helena"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "Category": "Food & Drink",
    "Question": "The eggs of this sturgeon are the preferred form of caviar.",
    "Answer": "Beluga"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the motto of the three muskateers",
    "Answer": "All for one & one for all"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the flower that stands for: a heart ignorant of love",
    "Answer": "White rosebud"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What nationality was the sculpture Brancusi",
    "Answer": "Romanian"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "Category": "Toys & Games",
    "Question": "Charles Darrow based his game upon the 1904 \"The Landlord's Game\".",
    "Answer": "Monopoly"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who sang \"I Want My MTV\" on the Dire Straits song \"Money For Nothing\"?",
    "Answer": "Sting"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "What country did poinsettias originally come from? (Mexico,Us, Spain ,Brazil)",
    "Answer": "Mexico"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Who Starred As Cole Porter In The 1945 Film Night & Day",
    "Answer": "Cary Grant"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Before Hitting The Big Time As A Singer & Tv Personality What Was \"Perry Como's \" Profession",
    "Answer": "A Barber / Hair Dresser"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "What was finally a top ten hit for Ce Ce Peniston on its 1992 Re-Release",
    "Answer": "Finally"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Seventeen thousand how many camels carried the 117,000 volumes of abdul kassem ismael's library",
    "Answer": 400
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Under Michigan State law who are officially classed mechanics",
    "Answer": "Dentists"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Medieval monks invented this stopper, necessary for champagne",
    "Answer": "Cork"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In the body luteinizing hormone is produced by what gland",
    "Answer": "Pituitary"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "Category": "Food & Drink",
    "Question": "What colour is chablis?",
    "Answer": "White"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "Football: The Denver ____?",
    "Answer": "Broncos"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What are the stars in traditional Cornish Star Gazey pie",
    "Answer": "Pilchards eyes"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is raku",
    "Answer": "Japanese pottery"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Proverbially it was a bold man who  first ate what",
    "Answer": "An Oyster"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "Category": "Food & Drink",
    "Question": "Where is the oldest distillery in the world?",
    "Answer": "The Old Bushmills, Cty Antrim"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What countries days include Fire day, Water day and wood day",
    "Answer": "Japan Tue Wed Thu"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In golf what would you put in your shag bag",
    "Answer": "Practice Balls"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Constance Markiewicz, Became The Worlds First Ever What In 1918?",
    "Answer": "First British Female MP"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "Which Modern Gymnastics Event Made Its First Appearance At The 2000 Sydney Olympics",
    "Answer": "Trampolining"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Burning potassium has what colour flame",
    "Answer": "Purple"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who directed the monochrome (sepia) sequences at the beginning and end of \"the wizard of oz\" (1939)",
    "Answer": "King vidor"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "Who Became premier of Cuba in 1959.",
    "Answer": "Fidel Castro"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "According to the song what did my true love give to me on the fifth day of Christmas",
    "Answer": "Five Gold Rings"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the cap on the fire hydrant called",
    "Answer": "Bonnet"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": "What is the capital of Philippines ?",
    "Answer": "Manila"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "Who Originated The Uncertainty Principle",
    "Answer": "Heisenberg"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What dodgers and cubs first-baseman dropped baseball to take up actin",
    "Answer": "Chuck"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which usical instrument was invented by Henry Schluter?",
    "Answer": "Vibraphone"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "How long is a silver anniversary",
    "Answer": "25 years"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Johnny Marr Teamed Up With Which Former New Order Member To Form The Band Electronic",
    "Answer": "Bernard Sumner"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Test of metal or ore for ingredients and quality",
    "Answer": "Assay"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is a woolly bear",
    "Answer": "Caterpillar"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the name of the telescope that was placed in orbit in the eighties?",
    "Answer": "Hubble"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Where was The Beast, the first mobile robot, developed",
    "Answer": "Johns hopkins"
  }
]